1. What does CSS stand for?
   Correct: Cascading Style Sheets
2. Which property is used to change the background color?
   Correct: background-color
3. How do you select an element with id 'header'?
   Correct: #header
4. Which property is used to change the font size?
   Correct: font-size
5. How do you make text bold in CSS?
   Correct: font-weight: bold
6. Which property is used for text color?
   Correct: color
7. What is the default value of the position property?
   Correct: static
8. Which property is used to create space between elements?
   Correct: margin
9. How do you make a list not display bullet points?
   Correct: list-style-type: none
10. Which property is used to change the text alignment?
   Correct: text-align
11. What is the correct syntax for a CSS comment?
   Correct: /* comment */
12. Which property controls the space inside an element?
   Correct: padding
13. How do you select all <p> elements?
   Correct: p
14. Which value makes an element invisible?
   Correct: All of the above
15. What is Flexbox used for?
   Correct: Layout design
16. Which property is used for rounded corners?
   Correct: border-radius
17. What does the z-index property control?
   Correct: Stack order
18. Which unit is relative to the viewport width?
   Correct: vw
19. How do you apply CSS to multiple selectors?
   Correct: Separate with comma
20. Which property is used for CSS Grid?
   Correct: display: grid
